

NIKHIL KHEMANI

S O F T W A R E SUPPORT EXECUTIVE

PROFILE:

Motivated with 8 years of sales expertise and 1.5 years of experience in Software Support. Recognized for accessing operational needs and developing solutions to save costs, improve revenues, and drive customer satisfaction. Resourceful and well-organized with excellent leadership and team-building record. Customer-oriented with strong and leading high-performance teams to meet or exceed objectives. Dedicated hardworking and self motivated.

CONTACT

+91 913-021-4794

✓ heisnikxy@gmail.com

Ahmedabad

SKILLS

- HTML + CSS + JavaScript
- React + JSX + npm
- Project Management Skills
- · Critical Thinking
- · Proficiency in Time Management
- · Communication Skills

EDUCATION

AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE ENGINEERING

2012 - 2015

I've done Aircraft Maintenance Engineering at Thakur Institute of Aviation Technology (Mumbai) (OJT Dropout)

Stream: Mechanical (Heavy Aircraft/Jet Engine)

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER APPLICATION

2022 - Present

I'm currently pursuing BCA at Dr. Babasaheb Ambedkar Open University

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT AT MASAI

EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE SUPPORT EXECUTIVE

Humani Media Consultancy 2022 - Present

- · Software Support Specialist.
- Provides tech support to users.
- Diagnose and troubleshoot software and hardware problems and help our customers install applications and programs.
- Provides expert services for customers to resolve issues and problems using remote desktop connections to provide immediate support.

MANAGER HEAD

Hema Creation

2017 - 2022

I was leading a team of 6 people in the sales department and also uploading digital catalogs for online e-commerce websites

SALES DEPARTMENT

Shivkrupa Furniture 2015 - 2017

In Shivkrupa Furniture my job profile was to provide the best guidance to customers about the products and help them with the product knowledge.

HARD SKILLS	100%	
SOFT SKILLS	80%	